Let's play the king game!
Near the end of summer break,
Misuzu and Carol came to spend the night.
I'm the king.
Huh?
And what's your order?
Tomo-chan has to do an
impersonation of Misuzu-chan.
What?! I can't impersonate Misuzu!
Okay, then I will.
Wait, why?!
I'll slaughter you socially.
I'm the king.
Yikes! Misuzu?!
I'm scared.
Okay, Tomo... You will go to the
fireworks show with Junichiro.
Huh?
King
Just the two of you this time.
When I throw a jab or a straight,
it always lands
But when I'm aiming for your heart,
I miss every time
Parallel, zigzagging, awkward, incoherent
When you look my way and move closer to me
I know it doesn't mean the same thing for you
But I wish we could stay like this forever
My changing feelings are driving me crazy
The moment you turn to face me,
take that! Telepathy
If only we could feel the same thing
I want to kick this pesky subtlety away
I want to know everything,
I want to know everything
I can't fool you forever
I can't keep this hidden
I want to shout out my secret, AHHH
Take that! Telepathy
Te-te-te-telepathy
Telepathy
The Night of the Summer Festival
"The Night of the Summer Festival."
D-Do you want to go see
the fireworks with me?
The fireworks?
Are those two gonna be with us again?
N-No! This time... just us two!
It'll be just us two.
Just us, huh?
Okay. Let's go.
Huh? He doesn't seem that excited.
Normally, he's like...
Man, I can't wait for the fireworks!
Should we really just let
things go on like this?
Like what?
The way Jun-kun and Tomo-chan are going,
they could end up getting together
like a normal guy and girl.
I was just wondering, would that
really be a good thing?
Shut up.
Just me and Tomo seeing the fireworks, huh?
I'm so happy. Like, more than I should be.
I love you, Jun!
Nah... She didn't mean
it that way... I'm sure.
Probably.
I feel like Jun's been acting weird lately.
When we went to the beach,
he didn't seem all that into it.
And just today... Could it be...
Summer exhaustion?
It's not.
When Tomo came to me to
tell me she loved Junichiro,
I gave her a hackneyed response
without even thinking about it.
Then why don't you try being more feminine?
And then Tomo dedicated herself to
the idea way more than I expected.
She even started showing interest
in more girlish leisure activities.
Maybe I really was wrong, like Carol said...
About what I should have said to
her back then as her best friend.
But I have no intention of going back now.
If I use him, Tomo and
I can do more... more...
Huh?
The Day of the Fireworks Show
Jun, you're going to see the
fireworks with Tomo-chan?
Yeah.
Good luck!
Thanks.
I'm hyped, but also not.
I'm happy, but also anxious.
I'm gonna go figure out what
this annoying feeling is.
Misuzu-chan, let's go watch the fireworks.
No.
Aw, c'mon. Ko-chan's coming, too.
Senpai's going? Then wouldn't
I be a third wheel?
If it means you end up alone, I'm not going.
Hmph.
What's your deal?
Sorry, Jun! Were you waiting long?
Mom told me I should wear this...
and it took a while to put it on.
What's wrong? You okay?
Sorry, I'm fi—
Actually... maybe not quite.
Are you feeling sick?
Goldfish Scooping
I'm back again this year, old fart.
Hey, Jun-bo. Tomo-chan's
not with you this year?
Did you forget what I look like?
What?! You're Tomo-chan?!
Something wrong with that?
I can't believe the stall-destroying
demon of the summer festival
grew up to be such a beauty.
Gotta save this moment.
Oh? Is that what you guys have
been calling me behind my back?
Calling all vendors! They're back!
Tomo-chan and Jun-bo?!
Try not to die of shock when you see this!
On my way with provisions
Roger!
Tomo and Jun-bo are here
Wh-What?!
Th-This is that out-of-control tomboy?!
She looks like a gravure idol in a yukata!
I'll take one dish of ammo.
Yeah, but...
1st Prize
She's still the same on the inside!
I wish you'd said that sooner.
That's my secret technique, the Triple Shot!
You're holding hands so naturally.
Yeah. If I let go of her hand...
See?
I can get her back pretty quickly, though.
You've got it rough, huh?
That looks like you, Ko-chan.
What does?
This is Ko-chan.
Uh... it is?
This is Tomo-chan.
She'll get mad at you.
Misuzu-chan.
I'll get mad at you.
Take whichever one you want.
Hey, check it out, Jun!
These handcrafted candies are incredible!
Huh?
Who's Jun? Your boyfriend?
I-I don't have a boyfriend!
Oh, so you're free, huh?
Come hang out with us, then.
What the hell?
She does have a boyfriend.
Uh... Jun...
Thanks for helping me—
Sorry.
Huh?
I'm sure you could've
handled that by yourself.
Jun...
I butted in again.
Would it...
Would it kill you to let me thank you?!
What the hell do you mean,
I could've handled it myself?!
I might be strong in a fight, but there
are some things I just can't do!
S-Sorry...
Yeah, so... I'm gonna thank you now!
Listen good!
S-Sure.
Thank you.
I'm really glad you were there for me.
Thanks.
I think the fireworks are about to start.
I know a great spot to watch from.
O-Okay...
What... was that?
Something's definitely off about him today.
Is he... actually starting to notice me now?
If he is...
Maybe this time, I can get
my feelings across for real.
Welp, I bought it.
Do I look cute?
I'm even more of a
third wheel than I thought.
Is that...
I'm not letting you go anywhere.
Let's go.
That's why she invited me along?
This squishy bitch...
If I'm gonna tell him, I should
do it before the fireworks start.
Now's my only chance.
Jun!
L-Listen...
What?
I feel like I can make him
understand this time.
And if that happens,
what we have now will end.
Our "now" will end,
and "something" will begin.
What is it?
But what is "something"?
It's not like there's even anything I want.
I just wanted to make Jun my own.
Now isn't the time.
There's no chance for us right now.
They're pretty, huh?
Yeah.
That was a lot of fun!
I still haven't figured out what
this feeling I have for Tomo is.
Hey, Jun!
Let's do this again!
But I did figure out one thing.
I can't...
have a real punching match
with Tomo ever again.
The Distance
Between Them
"The Distance Between Them."
What's wrong, Tomo-chan?
You're starting the new term
in unusually low spirits.
Junichiro again?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure Jun's starting
to be careful around me.
Isn't that good?
No, the way he's doing it is just...
Hey, Tomo. Mornin'.
His pinky?!
Let's go to school.
Frankly, it's creepy!
That's frank, all right.
Is that how it's always
gonna be from now on?
What am I gonna do?
Things with Tomo-chan and
Jun-kun are starting to change.
Just like you planned it, Misuzu-chan! Right?
You don't seem very happy, though.
Just shut up.
What is that squishy bitch trying to do?
She doesn't seem like she wants
to get in the way, but...
And Tomo...
She's gonna have to grow
up one of these days.
Same goes for Junichiro.
So what's wrong with things changing now?
To go from best friends with no
reservations around each other to lovers...
If that happens to those two...
I'll...
Man, shit's been so dull for us lately.
It's all because of that giant woman!
We gotta get back at her somehow!
That's...
Not you!
Yo.
Got a sec?
Don't touch me.
What the hell is this weird intensity?!
Hey!
I know all of your faces now.
Misuzu-chan, what're you doing?
Is she another one of Aizawa's buddies?
She has nothing to do with me or Tomo.
She's just a classmate.
Fine, then. Let's go.
Wait!
What? You want us to play with you, t—
You okay?! Hang in there, man!
Move, now!
What are you doing?
Where the hell did they go?!
Over there!
Well, what to do now?
Yeah?
It's me.
Gundo?
I don't remember giving you my number.
I'm in kind of a tight spot right now.
Come help me.
I'm at the abandoned
factory near the school.
Carol's here, too.
And don't tell Tomo.
I won't.
Hey, Jun!
I'm gonna go ahead and leave.
I've got stuff to do.
What stuff?
Hang on.
Where are you going with that
bloodthirsty look on your face?
Damn it.
Misuzu and Carol?!
That's really bad!
Yeah, but I can take care of it by myself.
Screw that! I'm going, too!
You think I'm that useless?
You idiot! It's not because
I don't have faith in you!
Those two are my friends!
I can't just let someone else go help
them while I wait around in safety!
Oh, yeah. That's the kind of
person my best friend is.
Carol?
Are you angry?
Just so you know, it's not my
fault you fell on your face.
Hmph.
I don't talk to people
I have nothing to do with.
Oh, that's why.
I just said that
because I thought things would be
even worse if you got involved, too.
I mean, I do think of you as...
something like a friend, after all.
Misuzu-chan!
I thought I might be able
to pull it off that time.
It's not gonna be that easy.
Also, you're filthy.
Found you.
I've been dying to see you.
Heya, Senpai.
Why don't we go somewhere
else and have some fun?
I guess Tomo-chan showed up after all.
That's just who she is.
I had a feeling she'd come.
I love Tomo-chan for being like that.
You don't, Misuzu-chan?
Damn it, Jun!
I told you, this is my fight!
Yeah, yeah.
I'll leave this two the two of them
and look for Carol and Gundo-san.
Come on, take those dirty
clothes off already.
But it's cold.
There you are!
Caro—
Misaki-senpai?
Oh, it really is Ko-chan!
You're the only one left.
It's about time you learned your lesson.
Damn it!
Hey, you punks.
What did you do to Carol?!
Was it you?
Are you the one who did
indecent things to Carol?
Misaki-senpai? What's wrong?
Wh-What are you talking about?!
Don't you play dumb with me!
She's such a sweet, pure girl, and you...
And you...!
Ko-chan got angry for my sake!
Just correct the misunderstanding
before someone dies.
You were just changing clothes?
Yep, that's right.
How could I make such a stupid mistake?
That made me happy, though. Thank you.
Tomo, you can go on home.
What are you gonna do?
There's something I need
to talk to him about.
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
Yeah? Okay, then.
You sure about this?
If Misuzu says she'll be fine, she'll be fine.
Let's go.
What do you wanna talk about?
Want me to play with you?
Look at you, acting tough the moment
Tomo and Junichiro are gone.
It's almost refreshing how weak you are.
What?!
But weak or not,
even a petty thug like you must
know about the Aizawa Dojo, right?
All the bad guys around
here know about that!
The legendary delinquent leader, Aizawa Goro,
and his band of wack jobs who
want to change the world!
Well, Tomo is his only daughter.
P-Please forgive me! I had no idea!
I heard you're gathering all the punks
in this area to start up a team.
If any of your buddies or wannabe
gangsters mess with my friends again,
I'll make sure you're the
one who pays for it.
It's not like I can control them all!
Do you know how many there are?!
Whether you can or not, you'd better.
Devote your entire body and
soul to protecting them.
P-Protecting... who?
My friends and me... and yourself.
You're as ruthless as ever, I see.
Oh, Junichiro. You're still here?
You should've threatened them
before they came after you.
It didn't occur to me.
Liar.
You ran to this particular
place on purpose, didn't you?
He tried to mess with me and my friend.
I wasn't going to let him
walk away unscathed.
You...
are not gonna die a pleasant death.
I never expected a pleasant
death in the first place.
Why did you bother waiting for me?
Well, you are still a girl, you know.
So is Tomo.
Yeah, but...
With her, it's not about
being a guy or a girl.
I don't want to hear it.
Not from you or that squishy bitch.
Squishy?
Aizawa
I'm heading out.
I really blew it yesterday.
I lost my cool and acted
like a savage again.
And just when he was starting
to notice me lately.
Morning, Tomo.
Jun...
What's wrong? Let's go to school.
That's it, Jun! That's perfect!
That's perfect!
What are you talking about?
(This suspicious behavior is...)
Hey, you know, I'm all mixed up
It's too complicated, I'm freaking out
I want to look cute to you
(crazy, crazy, drive me crazy, and that's…)
So I'm plotting, bargaining,
sly, and stubborn
Dizzying love
Just tell him to look at you
And watch him stiffen up even more,
because you're both so awkward
What? Even if we're alike in that way
It doesn't make me happy, 'cause it
means our love is going nowhere
Cloudy heart, swirling emotions—
I sense rain coming
So I partly open my umbrella,
then sneakily scoot closer to you
Please notice the curl of my
eyelashes as I keep blinking
And don't say I'm acting weird
All this plotting and bargaining
is my sly plan to look cute to you
Try to solve the riddle of
this soft, dizzying love
(Buzzing, fidgeting)
Listen, I might be a bit
tangled in my own web now
But once you unravel the mystery,
you'll see pure lo-love